

Contacts

a.bertash.dev@gmail.com

@AndrewBertash

github.com/ABertashDev

+38 096 728 37 24

Rivne, Ukraine

Skills

.NET 6, C# ASP .NET Core

EF Core

LINO

Razor Pages

Web API

MVC

nUnit

Swagger PostMan

HTML/CSS

English

Ukrainian

Russian

XML/JSON 1C Enterprise MS SQL Server

MySQL, T-SQL

PostgreSQL

Apache

TeamCity

Jira/Confluence

OOP **GIT**

REST API

SOLID, GOF

Agile, Scrum,

other software

development

methodologies

Languages

Certificate

B1 (Intermediate)

Native

Fluent

Andrii Bertash

JUNIOR .NET SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Profile

I am a software engineer with more than 6 years of commercial experience. I have organizational and problem-solving skills with a high level of self-motivation for work. I am easy and fast learn new technologies, frameworks, tools, etc.

I am an adaptable person. I have worked with different customers. They had disparate requirements and expectations of me. I have been able to adjust my possibilities and skills to meet each of their needs.

I am good at producing quality work in a team environment. In addition, I am very comfortable with public speaking.

Seeking to apply my experience and skills to benefit your company as a .NET developer. I am tired to be unrecognized developer and it is a reason why I want to switch to .NET technologies stack and become a part of the "true developers" community

Projects

Junior .NET 01.2023 - now Online recipe book

Online recipe book. ASP .NET Core, Web API, EF Core, LINQ, mySQL, HTML/CSS

Experience

1C Developer / Architect / PM / QA

03.2021 - now

Freelance projects, Rivne

Participated in many projects on the development and implementation 1C/BAS solutions for various types of businesses. Agreement work with the customers. Analysis and description of requirements. Connection trading equipment. Technical support

1C Developer / Architect / QA

08.2019 - now

ERP Data Service Ltd., Rivne

Franchisee team member. Development of solutions for automation of business processes and API integrations. Analysis and description of requirements. Connection of trading equipment

1C Developer

Renome-Smart Ltd., Rivne 06.2016 - 07.2019

Franchisee team member. Participated in many projects on the development and implementation of ERP and CRM systems based on 1C for various types of businesses. API integrations

Teacher/lecturer 05.2014 - 05.2016

GRAND (itosvita), Rivne

Teaching children according to the program, explanation of the material, checking the completion of tasks, maintaining documentation

Education

.NET Certification

05.2023

SoftServe Academy Certification

Certificate

Successfully passed .NET Certification

Certificate

GitHub

Junior .NET 06.2022 - 10.2022 **EPAM University**

Successfully completed .NET Summer Program 2022

Certificate

03 2021

09 2017

HS "SAB"

Professional in the implementation of BAS solutions for business

automation

Trainee QA SoftServe Academy

09.2018 - 10.2018

1C: Professional

BAS: Professional

1C Ukraine

Certificate

Professional in using 1C: Enterprise 8.3 platform mechanisms

Course "Test automation with Python"

Rivne State University of the Humanities

Diploma

Bachelor's Degree 09.2013 - 07.2017 Economic Cybernetics Bachelor's Degree (Diploma with honours)